squareberry.com 2016-12-04

# Mobile and Social Marketing Platform | Privacy Policy

Last updated January 1, 2011  

Welcome to Squareberry, a unique online calendar and social media application that integrates with multiple social network environments. The Squareberry application is developed by IVI Technologies Inc.; when this policy uses the term “we” and “our,” those terms mean IVI Technologies Inc.

**This privacy policy covers:**  

  * What information Squareberry collects.
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom we may share the information.
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact privacy@squareberry.com  

**Information Collection and Use**  
When you create an account on Squareberry.com we have access to some of your registered profile information via an application programming interface controlled by the social network. We use appropriate information to perform the Squareberry service. We mainly use your name and birth date, and the name and birth date of your friends.  
Squareberry collects information from you at several different points. We collect information when you create a new Squareberry account. We also collect information from you when you enter it into Squareberry, such as when you enter events into the application.     
The information we collect includes email addresses, time zones, country and events not included in the social network. This information along with social network ID number, session key and all information relating to the use of Squareberry features is stored on our secured servers for the purpose of providing the service.

**Information Sharing**  
Part of the service involves sharing your use of the service with your friends in accordance with the guidelines of the social network.  We will not sell, share, or rent any information obtained to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  

**Affiliates**  
Force 5, Inc.  

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads in our applications. We and advertising companies may use third party advertising technologies for targeted advertising in our application. In the course of advertisements being served to you, third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called “web beacons”) to help manage, optimize, and substantiate our online advertising.  
We do not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party advertising companies. However, through targeted advertising an advertiser may draw conclusions about personal characteristics of our users.  
Additionally, we may include certain personal demographic information of our users in the aggregate to advertisers or marketers for revenue generating opportunities. In these instances we take all precautions so the advertiser or marketer cannot specifically identify you through this data.  

**Third Party Services**  
We may partner with other parties to provide specific services. When you sign up for those services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide those services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing us services.  
****

**Choices About Your Information**  
In order for the Squareberry applications to work with one or more social networks, we require the following permissions, which were disclosed to you when you installed the Squareberry application:  
1.     Access to your basic information, which includes your name, and any other information you’ve shared with everyone;  
2.     Access to your birthday;  
3.     Access to your friends’ birthdays to the extent that they have shared them with you;  
In addition the following permissions may or may not have been required when you initially installed the Squareberry. If you have not previously provided the permission, or have since removed it, Squareberry will prompt you to accept the permission when you try to take advantage of a feature that requires the permission.  
1.     Access to your data when you aren’t actively using the Squareberry; and  
2.     Your email address or the ability to message you through the social network.  
****

**Correction of Your Information**  
Squareberry collects information from the social network and from our own online application, so correction of your information on the social network will result in correction of your information in the Squareberry application.  
Information that you manually entered into Squareberry can be corrected within the application. An example of this would be a birthday or event not provided by the social network.  
****

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law, or if we believe disclosure is necessary:  

  * To comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order;
  * To protect our rights and property;
  * To investigate and protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Squareberry;
  * During emergencies, such as when we believe someone’s physical safety is at risk.

**Links**  
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected through the Squareberry application. The application may contain links to other sites or applications. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites or applications. We encourage you to be aware when you leave Squareberry and to read the privacy statements of the web sites and applications you use.  

**Security**  
Squareberry takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit information via Squareberry, your information is protected both online and off-line. When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use an advanced encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, a lock or key icon appears on the bottom of your web browser.  

In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis (for example, our billing clerk or a customer support representative). Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.  
Our main servers are operated from a dedicated Internet hosting facility with state-of-the-art physical security features, including smoke detection and fire suppression systems, motion sensors, and 24×7 secured access, as well as video camera surveillance and security breach alarms.  

**Child Protection**  
Squareberry does not offer the application or any services to, or knowingly collect or solicit information from, anyone under the age of 13.  

**Security**  
If you have any questions about the security of Squareberry or you have questions about an email that appears to have been sent by us you can send an email to security@squareberry.com  

**Questions & More Information**  
If you have any questions or need more information regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Squareberry  
c/o IVI Technologies, Inc  
8672 sw 40th Street  
Suite 206  
Miami, FL 33155

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. When we post changes to this Policy, you will see the word “updated” next to the Privacy Policy link on the bottom of all pages within Squareberry. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how we use your personally identifiable information, we will provide a more prominent notice (such as a message when you first enter the application). We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
